He invested about 87 lakh rupees in his
[sangeet]
Maheshwar Fund,
withdrew it from Kundeshwar Fund
and bought a house worth around 10-11 lakh rupees
and had the house registered in his name saying
that I am the owner of this house
and
rented that house out for
125, two or three thousand rupees.
One of my friends
said that the stock market is also
gambling and
another of my friends said that in
20 years I have never made any
money from it.
Tata Steel of 20198 rupees is so
high in the market, even after the correction, it is standing at 1100 rupees today.
ONGC of 264 rupees
is ready to reach 3234 rupees. Hello friends, there is seven
which you must keep watching it rising, that
too is ready to go above 90 rupees.
And the biggest thing is
that this market is a market of hard workers, there is
absolutely no place here for those
who like to take shots.  Those who are
comfort-seeking people who want to live in dreams,
who want to make money,
but it should happen automatically, there is
no place for such people with such platonic thinking.
Here you have to read a lot all day,
know a lot, learn a lot
and that is why they always say the same thing, be it
Badshah Tahir Bhabhi or I like
Ramesh Sharma ji, that you should keep an
eye on the daily news
and I also believe that when your
knowledge and your vision is clear, then you will have
no problem in converting even a capital of Rs 11 lakh into Rs 1000 crore in Chittorgarh office figures, but the
first 5 to 10 years will be very difficult for you
and there will be many people who will make
fun of you, but what someone says
and what someone does not say, these things do not
matter much because people's job is to say,
but remember that those who had
taken their card from Bombay Stock Exchange, at
that time, in the beginning, the value of Rs 1 lakh, today that card is worth
Rs 607 100.  Bhairu, there are many, let me go,
I am not ready to go into those many things,
but I would like to give you three more big ones.
Asian Paints, Wipro, Infosys
and Rs 1 lakh, Rs 164, Rs
1 lakh within a year, Rs 1 lakh within 25 years, Rs
1 lakh within 167, Rs 1 lakh within 25 years, Rs 157, Rs 6
greens in the north. Come, how did Rs 95
turn into Rs 1 lakh? Add the Infosys IPO
in 25 years. 25 years have passed,
as three years have passed since my marriage,
I am ready to take a decision on those matters. If
someone says that it is gambling, I will not do it.
I am not ready to listen to these things now. There is
always loss here.
I will not come into traffic. I think those who
need some big money in the coming 10-20 years, they should
stay in this business, apart from any business they are doing, because whatever investment you make in any
shop, any house,
you get profit in that scenario.
Give some reason, if
you are opening a clothing shop, then you can do it only on Rs 15 lakh.  They are investing
and here they will come with ₹15, rather
collect 15 clothes, it has not even been 15 years that they will start
Yo Yo, is this some kind of drama, is this a joke,
what is it, you are ready to
earn 20 thousand rupees a month by investing 1500000 rupees there,
you have to invest this 15 lakhs, then
which grandmother is yours and on top of that she says
that no son, this work should not be done,
if you
hear anything yesterday and the day before yesterday,
I was hurt by this and
those people who tried their pimples are
calling me today, I am not picking up the phone
because I have blocked some people
and I am not picking up some others,
but I can definitely tell you once,
you are in India and being a citizen of India, the
whole world
is ready to take advantage from here, you have missed that Friday,
you do not miss About India,
you do not miss Nestle, you have
understood quickly, you write Honeywell Agree, you do
not miss the sale, you have been freed from Tata Power, Tata Motors, will
you come sir  Don't miss it, remember there are
many companies like Bajaj Financier, Bajaj Finserv in the country,
companies like ICICI Lombard are not found anywhere in the country or the world,
only foreign companies are found
somewhere in the world, or there is an opportunity for you, there is an opportunity, there is an opportunity,
buy it, buy it,
stay put for a few days, for
24 years, then think about it and take a
decision, you will find many smart men
and smart people, don't listen to them
because they will be fools like us, listen to me,
if you run any ₹1000 Kabir Saifi for 10 years,
tell me how much money will you accumulate in 10 years,
punishment against India and the world too, stop,
I give you a grant, from here
you will be cheated, so
don't listen to the words of smartphones,
smartphone people, those who keep
you away from the market, they cannot be your friends,
they are your enemies for sure, they are your
enemies for sure.